Guide to the Dell Williams papers, 1922-2008.
Williams, Dell papers, 1922-2008
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dell Williams papers, 1922-2008.
7676
Dell Williams, 1922-2015
4.9 cubic feet
Correspondence, subject files, audiotapes, videotapes, ephemera.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Records of Eve's Garden, including mission statement, catalogs and letters sent out to customers, articles about the business, and flyers for sexuality workshops held at Eve's Garden and elsewhere; material from a speaker's bureau Williams organized called New Feminist Talent; and articles and writing on sexuality that Williams collected, including a first edition of Betty Dodson's 1972 "Liberating Masturbation." Also, some of Williams' personal papers, including a 1974 appointment book.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
A former actress and advertising account executive, in 1974 Dell Williams founded Eve's Garden, a business guided by a feminist and sex-positive philosophy that offered for sale vibrators, books, and other products to enhance and liberate women's sexuality. At first, she operated a mail order business, and later she also opened a storefront in New York City. The first store of its kind, Williams advertised it as a "feminist sexuality boutique and mail order catalog created by women for women and their partners." Williams was influenced by the writing of Wilhelm Reich and the work of sexuality educator Betty Dodson and by her experience organizing a Women's Sexuality Conference for the New York chapter of the National Organization for Women in 1973.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records of Eve's Garden, including mission statement, catalogs and letters sent out to customers, articles about the business, and flyers for sexuality workshops held at Eve's Garden and elsewhere; material from a speaker's bureau Williams organized called New Feminist Talent; and articles and writings on sexuality that Williams collected, including a first edition of Betty Dodson's 1972 "Liberating Masturbation." Also, some of Williams' personal papers, including a 1974 appointment book.
Also, correspondence with others involved in aspects of sexual liberation and feminism, including Helen Robinson, Alice Ladas, Linda Bisgaard, and Sandra De Sando, and clippings, research notes, and drafts of writing they shared on women's sexual response and other topics. Also, correspondence from Lynette Brannon who in 1977 was running the first Eve's Garden "franchise" in Austin, Texas. Videos entitled "Increasing Male Sexual Potency" by Dr. Anthony A. Zaffuto and "500 Unusual Sex Practices" produced by the Institute for Advanced Study of Human Sexuality. Also an antique vibrator from ca. 1911-1920.
Books, videotapes, audiotapes, and manuscript materials on topics about sexuality, spirituality, feminism, and writing. Personal and business correspondence relating to sexuality and Eve's Garden. Writings by Sally Miller, sex and health columnist. Also, a glass award from An Uncommon Legacy Foundation; a tennis cup and a medal that Dell's parents won in tennis tournaments; clippings and a book describing Dell's brother Lorenzo's experience in a plane crash; a vibrator.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Williams, Dell, 1922-; Afua, Queen.; Bisgaard, Linda.; Brannon, Lynette.; De Sando, Sandra.; Dodson, Betty.; Ladas, Alice Kahn.; Miller, Sally, 1968-.; Eve's Garden (New York, N.Y.)
Subjects:
Feminism.; Sex oriented businesses.; Erotica.; Female orgasm.; Masturbation.; Spirituality; Vibrators.; Women--Sexual behavior.; Women-owned business enterprises.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Customer correspondence (Box 5) is RESTRICTED until January 2079, except by permission of archivist. Customer identities are to be kept confidential.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
Materials in Series I are listed here chronologically where possible and alphabetically otherwise. Materials in Series II and III are listed alphabetically.
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting program: Human Sexuality Collection.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Eve's Garden and Dell Williams
Boxes 1-3, 5-6, 7
This series includes material about the operation and philosophy of Eve's Garden: Dell Williams's notes and writing about the start, purpose, and goals of the business, her series of articles "Sexually Speaking", some audiotaped interviews and lectures by her, publicity files, lists of the product line, and files about product development and events sponsored by the store, as well as Williams's appointment books. Also included are some of Williams's personal writings, résumés, and correspondence. The series also contains materials pertaining to Dell's immediate family: awards won by her tennis-playing parents, correspondence with her brother Lorenz when both were in the army in 1946, and materials concerning Lorenz's experience in a plane crash in 1972. In addition are files about close friend Betty Dodson, and about the 1973 NOW Women's Sexuality Conference, which was pivotal in Williams' life. Customer correspondence is restricted until 2079.
Personal
Eve's Garden
Betty Dodson
Interfaith Ministry
Series II. Colleagues, Correspondents, and Subjects
Boxes 1-3, 6
This series, arranged alphabetically, includes the correspondence and information she saved from numerous people and organizations involved in sexual liberation, spirituality, feminism, and sex education. Included are drafts of articles numerous writers shared with her.
Sexuality
Spirituality
Feminism and Other
Series III. Clippings and Print Material
Boxes 2-3, 6
This series consists of various articles she saved from magazines, newspapers, and pamphlets.
Series IV. Audiovisual Material
Box 6-8
This series consists of videotapes and audiotapes on various sexual subjects, collected by Williams. Audiovisual material featuring Williams or Dodson is listed in Series I.
Series V. Merchandise
Boxes 2-4
This series contains items that have been products at Eve's Garden or objects that Williams collected.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Eve's Garden and Dell Williams
  - Personal
    - Tennis medal from D.W.'s father, 1922 (Box 2)
    - Silver tennis cup from D.W.'s mother: "Susan Zetlin, Women's Single, 1925" (Box 2)
    - Photographs, 1936-1970s (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Periwinkle (high school yearbook; see p. 73), January 1940 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - "Our Day", scripts from radio show in army (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Zetlin, Lorenz (D.W.'s brother)--letters to D.W. while in army, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Williams, Dell--Theater Résumé and Actress's Working Permit, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - "Ideals Ideals Ideals?" Bound poem by friend of Dell, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Bioenergetics (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Scrapbook with D.W.'s work in journalism and advertising, circa 1951-1956 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Picture-story about Ossie and Ruby Davis by D.W. and husband, circa 1960 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - D.W.--Essay about starting therapy, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Cards, letters, poetry from friends, 1969-2007 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Zetlin, Lorenz--Résumés, professional life, circa 1970s (Box 6, Folder 88)
    - D.W.--letter to therapist, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Zetlin, Lorenz--Crash of Eastern AirLines Flight 401, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - NOW-New York Women's Sexuality Conference, June 9-10, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - NOW Women's Sexuality Conference, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - NOW Women's Sex Conference, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - D.W. lecture: "Are you a radical feminist?" (for NOW conference?), 1973? (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Photographs, circa 1973-1996 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Picture of President Roosevelt, marked "my favorite President!" by Dell (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - The Liberated Woman's Appointment Calendar, 1973, 1974, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Jacqui Ceballos interview with Dell, Part 1 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Interview part 2 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Interview part 3 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - D.W.: letter to Majority Report, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Zetlin, Sarah (D.W.'s mother)--essay by D.W. about, circa 1974 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - NOW-letter welcoming D.W. to New York NOW Advisory Council, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 90)
    - Miscellaneous personal and work-related correspondence, 1976-2008 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - D.W. essay: "The Stapler, or To Give or Not to Give" (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - D.W. essay: "Irving Ravages East Coast" (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - D.W.--poetry (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Dell Williams--list of goals (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Bisexuality correspondence, 1981-1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Whole Life, p.21 D.W. article, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - "Dell Williams" International Who's Who in Sexology, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Foremost Women of the 20th Century (D.W. listed), 1988 (Box 6, Folder 91)
    - D.W. radio and TV appearances, circa 1990-2006 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - D.W. speech: Lust conference at NYU School of Law, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - D.W. speaking engagements and press releases, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - D.W.: Writings on bisexuality (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - D.W.: Writings on vibrators, Eve's Garden, feminism (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - D.W.: Writings on masturbation and vibrators (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - "To Explore, Define and Celebrate Our Own Sexuality", article by Dell Williams (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - "Sexually Speaking": A series of articles by Dell Williams, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - "Sexually Speaking": D.W.'s column in Sappho's Isle (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - "The Bisexual Feminist" and "Switch Hitter" correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Camcorder workshop registration, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Letter from Dell in Lilith, Winter 1993 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - An Uncommon Legacy Foundation: Uncommon Woman Award given to D.W., 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Uncommon Woman Award given to D.W. (glass plaque), 1994 (Box 2)
    - Williams, Dell--Résumé, circa 1998 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Letter to Hillary Rodham Clinton, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - D.W. essay: "Duck Pond", 1999 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Writings, correpsondence with Sue Kain, Taproot magazine, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Head shot and resume, circa 2000 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Letter to Jacqui Ceballos reflecting on Feminist Expo 2000, Baltimore, M.D. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - "Finding Dell," journal entry, February 22, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 97)
    - Veteran Feminist Educators - Recognition of D.W. and others, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Flint, Rebecca: Master's Thesis about sex toys; with D.W.'s comments, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Memorial Service for Sarah Zetlin, Dell's mother, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Eichna, Charlotte and Moore, Christopher - "Who Sex Offenders Are" in West Side Spirit and D.W.'s response (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - National Women's Hall of Fame--Rosa Parks, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Bartlik, Barbara and Weill Cornell Medical Center--invitation to D.W., 2004 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - SAGE Conference, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Response to 20/20 program about female sexuality, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Dell's biography, Revolution in the Garden, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - Corrections to proof copy of book, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Invitation to NOW Susan B. Anthony Awards (D.W.: recipient), 2005 (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - D.W.: honored by Veteran Feminists of America, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Berman, Laura: "Williams did a lot for women", 2005 (Box 6, Folder 93)
    - Veteran Feminists of America event to honor Dell, October 30, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Feminists Who Changed America event, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Notes on Dell's writings and work, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Miscellaneous notes (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Correspondence to Cornell (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Prints of original drawings by Raymonde Paquet-Blain (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Dell Williams Interview: Voices in the Wind #770911, National Public Radio/Kernis, tr. 8016a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - Dell Williams Interview: New School, sides 1 and 2, May 11, 1983; tr. 8017a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - Dell Williams Interview: New School, side 3: multiple male orgasms, May 11, 1983; tr. 8018a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - Dell Williams Interview: unlabeled, tr. 8019a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - "Lecture by Dell Williams at New Life Expo", 1979; tr. 8013a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - "Celebrating the Sexual Goddess Within"--talk by D.W. at New Life Expo, 1991 or 1992; tr. 8037a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - "Celebrating the Sexual Goddess Within"--talk by D.W., tr. 8049a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - Whole Life Expo--D.W. lecture "Sexuality and self love", 1987 or 1989; tr. 8029a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - "Revolting Behavior Keynote Panel", November 1, 1997; tr. 8039a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - "Speakout to the NOW Sexuality Conference", June 1973; tr. 8025a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - "French Toast for Breakfast," Mary Anne Cohen, CSW, Interview by Dell Williams, November 28, 1990; tr. 8014a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
  - Eve's Garden
    - About Eve's Garden (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Information about Eve's Garden (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - D.W. notes on Eve's Garden Philosophy (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Statements of Purpose (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Dell's account of store inception and expansion and struggle, circa 1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Essay about start of Eve's Garden (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Eve's Garden binder 1-1 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Eve's Garden binder 1-2 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Eve's Garden binder 1-3 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Eve's Garden Newsletter Fall 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Eve's Garden Newsletter Winter 1990 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Eve's Garden Newsletter Spring 1992 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Eve's Garden Newsletter Fall 1994--20th Anniversary Edition (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Images used for making Eve's Garden T-shirts sold at the store, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Store flyer insert with sale of Prelude 2 Vibrator, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Hartman, Bunne--Correspondence with Dell, 1975-1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - E.G.: Encouraging note, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Starting the Newsletter, including receipt from Kate Millett, 1976-1979 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Hartman, Bunne--Correspondence--original copies, circa 1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Workshops presented by Williams/Eve's Garden, 1977, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - "Manual" draft by D.W., Bryce Britton, "Guide to masturbation and vibrator use", 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Drafts of "The Pleasure Right Principle", by D.W. and Bryce Britton, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Peacock, Patricia, artist, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Eve's Garden brochure, circa 1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Carten, Marilyn--business correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Letter explaining financial crisis with Venture Capital, circa 1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Aaron Graphic Design publicity materials, circa 1983 (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Nippon Kodo, Inc. incense, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Recognition for contributions to Lesbian/Gay Pride Day, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - AASECT Annual Meeting--Eve's Garden exhibit, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Phil Donahue Show, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 102)
    - Eve's Garden flyers and advertisements, circa 1990 (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Eve's Garden--form letters to customers, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Dildos, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Durga Bernhard, Eve's Garden publicity, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - On Our Backs--photocopies of Eve's Garden advertisements, 1991, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Business correspondence, 1986-1994, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Donations, 1991-1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Eve's Garden correspondence, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - GLBT and Sexual Health Organizations, Donations to and collaboration, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Bragar, Ellie--workshops through and indep. of Eve's Garden, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Ogden, Gina--Women Who Love Sex book events, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - E.G. Advertisement in On Our Backs, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Eve's Garden product line, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - NYC Gay/Lesbian Anti-Violence Project--donation, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - XOX/PK/Isa/Abbott, Paul/Body Electric/Erotic/Workshops with Eve's Garden, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Dorsey, Brenda and Bill--"The Woman's Video Guide to Orgasm", 1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Libido--photocopy of Eve's Garden ad, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Women's Video Guide, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Gutman, Jeremiah--lawyer, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - "Garden Views", 2005 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Eve's Garden Media Kit, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Eve's Garden publicity and Dell's notes., 1974-2006? (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Eve's Garden advertising proofs (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Britton, Bryce--correspondence, advertising (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Contact and advertising information for regional, bisexual, and foreign serials (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Cosmo Kama Sutra, Blurb about book (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Dildo Evaluations publicity and design (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Events, publicity (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Goldberg, Whoopi: D.W. letter to (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - "Have You Ever Seen an Orgasm?" video flyer (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Henes, Donna: The Queen of My Self Workshop (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Kuriansky, Judith--article in Beauty Digest (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Love Muscle Exerciser, Eve's Garden publicity for (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Order forms, sex and feminist related merchandise (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Public relations folder (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Publicity materials and catalogs (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - Request for support, E.G. (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Vagitone Vibrator sold by Eve's Garden (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Vibrator use, D.W. notes on (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Wolfe, Janet--writings and correspondence, 1975, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Write-ups and recognition, Eve's Garden (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Eve's Garden miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Professional correspondence., 1975-2008 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Customer correspondence [ RESTRICTED], 1975-2002 (Box 5, Folder 1-15)
  - Betty Dodson
    - Screw: The Sex Review Women's Issue, w/ drawings by Dodson, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Betty Dodson, "Liberating Masturbation", 1st ed., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Eve's Garden's reprints of Penthouse Forum article, "Insider Betty Dodson", February 1976 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Photos of Dell Williams and Betty Dodson, 1985-2000 (Box 6, Folder 94)
    - Eve's Garden's 15th Anniversary Woman of the Century Award, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - "An Evening with Betty Dodson" Workshop, presented by Eve's Garden, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Events with Betty Dodson presented by Eve's Garden, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - "Coming Out Strong" (Dodson article) (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Article about Betty Dodson and Magic Wand, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 79)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
    - Art: Women's Conference (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - "Selfloving," publicity for (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - About Betty Dodson (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Women's Sexuality Seminar, publicity for (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Dell: Writings about 1973 workshops with Betty Dodson (for "Sexually Speaking" article series?) (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Dodson, Betty (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Williams, Dell: Article about Betty Dodson (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Sexual drawings (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Phone sex, circa 2001 (Box 6, Folder 80)
    - "Betty Dodson on creating an...[?] for the Female Genitals", June 1973; tr. 8027a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - "Betty Dodson Interview", September 1991; tr. 8036a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
    - Betty Dodson Cunt Show, tr. 8023a; Cassette audiotape (Box 7)
  - Interfaith Ministry
    - Writings from New Seminary Courses (D.W.) (Box 6, Folder 81)
    - D.W.: Summaries of Lives of Mystics (Box 6, Folder 82)
    - The New Seminary Information, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 83)
    - Interfaith Ministry--some of Dell's favorite prayers, circa 2000 (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - The New Ministry--homework, circa 2001 (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - D.W.--Minister's Service and Reference Manual, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - Letter to Robin, inviting her to D.W.'s ordination as interfaith minister, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Series II. Colleagues, Correspondents, and Subjects
  - Sexuality
    - XVIIth World Congress of Sexology, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Alaví, Prinny (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Alman, Isadora (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - APA: Psychology and Human Sexuality (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Apaeros sampling, correspondence from Sylvia, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Apter, Michael (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Baker, Jo-Anne, correspondence regarding D.W. piece in "Sex Tip Book", 1998 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Barbach, Lonnie, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Bartlik, Barbara (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Bisgaard, Linda (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Body Electric School: Celebrating the Body Erotic for Women, 1993 and ? (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Brannon, Lynette: Austin Center for Human Resources, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Califia, Pat, Public Sex (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Center for Intimacy and Sexuality (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Chalker, Rebecca, "Secrets of Women's Sexuality Reading List" (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Chalker, Rebecca, "The Clitoral Truth" press release, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Chalker, Rebecca, circa 2003 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Clifford, Christen and Baby Love DVD and promo., 2006 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Colt, Ani, Includes "Self-Love as Spiritual Practice: Nine Keys for Learning to Love Yourself" (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Colton, Helen: Family Forum (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - "Community Sex Information": miscellaneous publications/flyers relating to sex/genitals (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - De Sando, Sandy, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - De Wicce, Patrikyia - correspondence and articles, 1988-1994 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - De Wicce, "A Letter from Patrikyia" draft, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - De Wicce, "To Love or Fuck: A Difference in Consciousness" draft, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - De Wicce, "Wilhelm Reich and the Function of Orgasm" drafts, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - De Wicce - Reich articles with notes to Dell, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - De Wicce, Erotic Earthbody, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - "Patrikyia De Wicce's Cunt Imagery", Margurite McAllister, in Eidos, v.1 no.3 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Patrikyia De Wicce's drawings of vulvas (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - De Wicce, "The Evolution of an Image" draft (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - De Wicce, "Orgasmic Flight", draft (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - Eichel, Edward: Coital Alignment Technique (CAT) (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Eichel, Edward: Coital Alignment Technique (CAT), 1992-2003 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Eroscillator - publicity and box (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Fawver, Patricia, "Erotic Integrity" (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - "Feminism, Sexuality, and Power" Mt. Holyoke conference, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Goldsmith, Amy and Britney Spears' lyrics., 2003 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Human Sexuality: A Psychosocial Perspective textbook brochure (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - International Society for the Study of Women's Sexual Health--conference brochures, 2004, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Kinsey (film), 2004 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Ladas, Alice--talk on WM-PR radio, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Leight, Lynn - Sex, Health, Education Center, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Lesbian Herstory Archives (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Libby, Roger, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Lightfoot-Klein, Hanny (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - Loulan, JoAnn, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 96)